看见保民了吗
啊
保民
谁
张保民
放开我
你这个臭哑巴
哎 保民 别打了
翠霞打电话 说磊子丢了
翠霞说磊子丢了
你儿子丢了
保民
你咋这么倔呢
你不签字
人家矿里不能开工生产
这村里其他人的补偿款都拿不到
给个面子 签了吧
不吃亏
签了吧
他一个人不签我们就都得等着
是啊 保民哥你就签了吧
不吃亏
你说有这么办事的么
给的不少了
你说这人咋这么倔呢
签了吧
都乡里乡亲的
就是啊
签了吧
酒你也喝了 肉也吃了
今天这事要是没个结果
你走不了
还敢在我这店里动手
服不服
张保民 你干啥呀你
出去
你给我出去啊你
汉生
你 你干啥呀你
村长 屋里搁不下了 我给您搁墙根了
行　快点卸 我一会还得进城呢
好勒
保民
刚回来
好久没见着你了
来
尝一根国外带的洋烟
来来来
尝一根
听说你在奉县那边挖煤呢
怎么样
一年能挣多少啊
等会儿
这是人家这个月给的补贴
正好碰上你就拿着吧
省的我再往你家跑了
磊子 是你吗
前天吃完早晨饭
磊子说要上后山
去遛遛羊去
我还跟他说让他早点回来
回来还得做作业呢
吸透了也没回来
我让检子给我出去找找去
栓子说哪儿都没有
哪儿都没找着人
就在后山坳里看见羊群
哪儿都没找着
同学们抓紧时间集合 快点
昌总 同学们都准备好了
咱们仪式开始吧
都说了不让你搞这些
多耽误孩子们学习赶紧散了吧
不耽误不耽误 这是应该的
您捐钱给我们建新校舍
得让孩子们知道
要好好念书 长大向您学习
听我的 赶紧散了吧
站在外边多冷啊 快散了吧
这
记者来了吗
来了
在外面等着呢
把他叫进来
就在这合张影吧
好
我去叫他
王校长等等
来 我们手稍微高一点
好 看镜头
微微笑一点 一 二 三
王总 那笔款什么时候清啊
上周就到期了
喂
又给我装信号差
截至收盘 上证综合指数跌破1270点…
徐先生
你这多麻烦
直接打我帐号里多好
徐律师
今天的法制报
你拿的这个是
这是弘昌矿业案的资料
王律师让我给他送过去
张哥 那天
就在那坡后面 那边
羊都在
没见着磊子
上周 我市中级人民法院就弘昌矿业集团
涉嫌非法采矿一案 进行了开庭审理
文杰 快趁热吃吧
我还有个菜马上就好
奶奶做的虾最好吃了
媛媛乖 多吃点
判定弘昌矿业为过失越界开采 责令其整改
该集团所辖矿区地处谷丰山脉
大小规模矿场有几十家
开矿挖掘所产生的纠纷和环造问题
一直受到大家的关注
奶奶做的虾可好吃了
王总他们还来不来
李总
尝尝吧 肉不错
我信佛 吃素
这个习惯可不好
羊
也吃素
剩下的让厨房炖了吧
真空打包好 给小宝寄去
孩子在国外 总闹着吃不惯
李总
我记得你孩子也在加拿大
我给你也弄一点
客气啦 你慢慢吃
我还有点事 先走了
李总
您的司机让我转告您
他不干了
昌万年 你要干嘛
昌总
你那事
真不是我举报的
你别冤枉人啊
矿上这点事
不是干这行的谁懂
谷丰山里大大小小十多个矿
不是用我的车就是用我的设备
只有你
跟我一点关系都不沾
老昌
真不是我
我
山北边那两个沟的采矿证
在你这吧
你把字签了
就算你赔偿我的
昌哥 你就饶了我吧
你知道
采矿证是不允许倒卖的
犯法的
我不要你的采矿证
我让你把公司卖给我
抓紧
在那卷肉切完之前
把字签了
你让它在屋睡呗
那是磊子给它裕的窝
什么时间不能保证啊
我都报案好几天了
你说你能帮我找到牛
现在连个影儿都没有
你说我都快急死了
您别激动
你知道不知道我有多着急
这牛是我们家的命根子啊
这我们办公的地方 您小点声
那孩子可以说话吗
那你是
你是不是在村里
得罪过什么人啊
我一大早啊
就去庙里烧香
求菩萨保佑咱们磊子能早点回来
还给你们请了点斋饭
赶紧吃吧
霞啊
你说
会不会是丁海
保民回来就去了
不在那
那你们到底差丁家多少钱
不少呢
每个月给点
这两个月不是看病吃药花好多钱
短人家两次
人家也没过来要来
那一只眼睛
能值多少钱
他这是讹上咱了
这生瓜蛋子你说
当初啊
早早听刘福的话
签字拿钱多好啊
妈
可别当着保民的面说这话
嗨
干什么的
找孩子
见过吗
到点了　上工啦
谷丰村的吧
路走得够远的了
吃饱了慢慢找吧
你们都给我
喂喂
你们都给我听好了
我不说第二遍
金泉矿业 被我们收购了
你们现在赶紧卷铺盖走人
这帮王八蛋 又来闹事来了
快点快点
你谁啊
你让我们走　我们就走啊
我们的工钱怎么办
这次看来要干仗了
你们这些无赖
天天来捣乱
真以为我们好欺负啊
打他们
前面这几个
给我狠狠的打
昌哥昌哥你听我说
车窗让干碎了
前挡风
一个后生
还挺猛
你们别打了
他不是我们矿上的
他是来找孩子的
别吵 闭嘴
说不是这矿上的
来找孩子的
这孩子
我见过
霞
我找胡半仙求了一卦
他说孩子没事肯定能回来
你拿着这个纸符
每天晚上烧上一张
三天后
磊子肯定能回来
保民在啊 我不敢说
你呀 偷偷的烧
哑巴
你的事先等会儿
这车窗是你砸的吧
你这也不够啊
这车是我们老板的
我也做不了主
要不
你跟我走一趟吧
后生 不能听他们的
他是在骗你的
徐律师好
文杰
你来一下
徐先生
关于弘昌矿业非法采矿案
我们有几个问题想跟你了解一下
请问你是怎么认识
弘昌矿业老板昌万年的
你在这等会儿
进来吧
前挡风基本上废了
他是个哑巴
不能说但是能听见
听说你孩子丢了
哪天丢的
你看见了
啊
十二号那天我从矿里回来
在镇上路口
看见有个小孩在那站着
我还纳闷呢
天都要黑了这孩子怎么还不回家
太晚了没看清楚
孩子叫什么
你是谷丰村的
老板问你话呢
你叫什么
在家种地
你让矿上的人都留意着点
好
行了 送他回去吧
那玻璃
不用你管了
等孩子找着了
到我矿上来干吧
您好 我们是市检察院的
你们昌总在吗
好的 请稍等
不会说话挺能耐
车玻璃不用你赔了
这顿打你少不了吧
下回见了爷爷躲着走 听见没有
好了
霞姐
在家没
栓子来啦 屋里坐
磊子还没回来吗
没有呢
霞姐
你腿上的水肿好点没
也不见好啊
这是我妈上次说的那个药
效果差不多还便宜
她现在都吃这个
让我开药的时候给你也带点
试试看管不管用
谢谢你妈
你看她都身体这么不好了
还老惦记着我
这井水的味是越来越大了
张哥也不在
找磊子去了
真是邪门了
这磊子能跑哪儿去呢
对了
那天张哥找完我回来
我想起个事
不知道跟磊子丢了有没有关系
臭哑巴 别让我再看见你
见你一次打你一次
栓子慢点走
给你妈问个好
没事 大娘您回去吧
张哥 您回来了
你这是咋了
你咋才回来
又跟谁打架了
你
人家栓子来找你有事说呢
那天晚上找磊子回来
我看见东面山沟里停一辆车
我看着也不像咱村的车
第二天就不见了
保民你这是咋的了
准是又跟谁打架了
都啥时候了你说
不是越野车
是一辆银灰色的轿车
对 差不多是这样的
银灰色的
你的回答和我们所了解的情况
有很大的出入
所以我们还会再来
我知道的早就说了
其他的事 你们应该去问徐律师
徐文杰已经不是律师了
他涉嫌在这个案件里制造伪证
妨碍司法公正
我们还会调查他
您应该慎重考虑一下
拖延不是办法
积极配合调查 主动检举
其实对你更有帮助
这一点
徐文杰是不会告诉你的
您好
您拨叫的用户正忙
请您稍后再拨
小兔子妈妈从山里
带回了野果和青菜
她回到家门口
敲响了木门
孩子们快开门
你们的妈妈回来啦
不对 重讲
这个不像兔子妈妈
孩子们
快开门
你们的妈妈回来啦
不像不像重讲
媛媛 乖啊
爸爸今天实在是太累了
改天再给你讲好吗
妈妈什么时候回来啊
妈妈
妈妈 她
等你上中学的时候就回来了
你骗人
都怨你
好了
靠边靠边靠边靠边
快点
喂
你们车出来了吗
快点 就在刚过大土坡一点
快点修啊
赶紧走
不行啊金哥 还得推下车
金哥
快
在这
快点
在这儿呢
快
快点儿
快快快
追
快快快快
分头追分头追
人呢
带着孩子跑不远
继续追
最近环保局查的有点严
要不　矿上先停一段时间
昌总
这两个月市场价格一直在涨
尤其金泉那个矿的产量还特别的高
如果我们不趁着行情
加速生产的话
就太可惜了
关键环保局　这要是
徐律师
你终于敢回电话了
我女儿是不是在你那
我的东西在你手上吧
什么东西
我不知道你在说什么
那就抱歉了
我也不知道你女儿在哪
在那呢
追
张保民
你赶紧把那女儿给我还回来
喂 喂
都给我上车
去他家等着
我不信他不回去
保民
保民这是去哪儿了
我正找你呢
在这儿呢
这回别让他跑了
快点啊
嘿
有没有看见一个男的跑过来
走
都走远了
孩子找着了吗
窝囊货
张保民
我实话告诉你啊
你儿子在我们手上
你要想见你儿子
你赶紧把那女孩给我还回来
你多带几个人
他一出现就把他抓住
去吧
孩子丢了
追了一座山都没有追上
还是让他给跑了
好像卡了根骨头
是他吗
不像
没戴眼镜
你找谁啊
这哥们儿是不是有病啊
来 该谁了
昌哥
您放心
他肯定得把女孩还回来
我骗他
说他儿子在我这
昌哥
老板
有电源吗 我充个电
桌子底下有插口
谢谢
对不起
干啥呢
磊子
保民
是你吗
张保民在家吗
这是个误会
你看到了
你儿子不在我这
我的手下为了让你交出女孩
骗了你
那女孩在哪
律师还能帮着找孩子呢
我们会接一些拐卖儿童的案子
拐卖
那还能找回来么
有可能有可能
不过这也不好说
我最近正好接了一个这样的案子
经过镇上的时候呢
看到了寻人启事
就给您丈夫打电话
想约他见一面
看能不能帮上什么忙
可他一直没来
您知道他有可能去哪吗
你跟他打电话说的
我们发短信说的
他打不了电话
怎么了 他
年轻时候跟人打架把舌头咬断了
从那以后就不愿意说话了
孩子没找着
自己还整丢了
你把我的公司弄成这样
我也就不追究你了
只要你把女孩还给我
喂
张保民吗
你能听见吗
我女儿在哪儿
你发短信告诉我好吗
喂
徐律师
我男人回来我就让他跟你联系
你一定要帮我们找找孩子呀
爸爸
妈
文杰 你在哪儿
媛媛找到了吗
你放心吧
我很快就能找着媛媛了
家里来了几个警察
说要跟你了解情况
我就把媛媛的事 跟人家说了
你等一下啊
徐文杰
你现在在哪
媛媛
张保民
我女儿在哪
没错 就是她
她在哪
都别动
把东西还给我
否则你再也见不到你女儿了
什么东西
他跟这件事儿没关系
你先放他走
拿不到东西
谁都别走
我不知道你想要什么
证据
什么证据
你是律师
你当然知道什么东西可以当作证据了
你先放他走
这是我们之间的事
你知道么
他儿子丢了
我知道他儿子丢了
别动
否则的话
你还想杀了他
你
你不是要证据吗
我就是证据
你报警了你
谢谢
别打了
我女儿在哪
媛媛
爸爸
媛媛 媛媛
媛媛
爸爸
爸爸带你回家
咱们回家
回家
警察来了
怎么办啊
你还有女儿要照顾
我相信你会有办法的
我知道非法采矿这个罪
挺严重的
我就派人去找律师
认识了徐文杰
如果被定罪
昌万年
最多是五年的有期徒刑
他请我帮他打赢这个官司
我就跟他说
如果这个案子全部能摆平的话
价钱随他开
我拿到资料以后
私底下
找到案子几个重要证人
买通了他们在法庭上作伪证
他把一切都打点好了
判决结果一出来
就是交点罚款的事
我挺满意的
很痛快的就给了他五十万现金
作为酬谢
徐律师
平时有什么爱好啊
也没什么爱好
您这弓
挺特别的啊
这个
有劲儿
我挺需要那笔钱的
还有什么要交代的
没有了
再想想 还有什么要说的
小孩儿
你这羊多少钱一只啊
没了
汉生
进去吃饭去
一天画啥呢 在这儿
跟你说话呢
进去吃饭去
"Winter, 2004."
Have you seen Baomin?
Who?
Baomin!
Zhang Baomin!
Let me go!
You stupid dummy!
Baomin, stop!
Xia just called. Lei is missing!
Xia said that she couldn't find Lei!
Your son is missing!
Baomin,
don't be like this.
If you don't sign,
they can't start mining.
Other villagers won't get
their compensation either.
Do me a favor. Just sign it.
It's a good deal.
Just do it
He'll keep us all waiting.
Yes, Baomin, just do it.
It's a good deal
I've never seen someone like this.
That's a lot of money.
Why are you so stubborn?
Just sign it!
Do us a favor!
Yes, that's right.
Just sign it.
Look, you drank the wine
and you ate the lamb.
If we don't finish this today,
nobody leaves.
You have the balls to pick a fight here?
Now, who's the boss?
Zhang Baomin! What are you doing?
Get out!
Are you deaf?
Get out of my place right now!
Hansheng
What's the matter with you!
Chief Liu, there's no room inside.
I'll put the rest beside the wall.
Hurry up! I'll head to town soon.
OK.
Baomin!
Are you just back here?
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Come!
Try one of these foreign cigarettes.
Come on
I heard you were working
as a miner in Feng County?
How's it going?
How much could you earn a year?
Wait a minute.
Here's this month's compensation.
Take it.
Or I have to go to your place again.
Lei, is that you?
The day before yesterday, after breakfast,
Lei said that he wanted to
take the sheep to the other side of the mountain.
I told him to come home early.
He hadn't finished his homework.
But he wasn't back by dark.
So, I sent Shuanzi to look for him.
Shuanzi couldn't find him anywhere.
He searched everywhere,
saw nothing but the sheep on the mountain.
Our son just disappeared.
Kids! Hurry up and assemble!
Mr. Chang, the students are ready.
Shall we start the ceremony?
I've told you to cut the show.
Better save their energy for study.
Let them go back.
No worries. It's our pleasure.
You gave us money for our new school buildings.
We should let the students know
that they need to work harder
and become a person like you.
Listen to me, send them back to the classrooms.
It's cold out there. Just let them go.
But...
Is the reporter here?
Yes.
He's waiting outside.
Call him in.
Let's take a picture here.
OK.
Let me call him.
Headmaster, wait a second.
Raise your hands a bit, please.
Very good. Now look into the camera.
Smile. Three, two, one.
Mr. Wang, when can you give us the money?
You should've done that last week.
Hello?
Not the weak signal again!
"News about the stock market crash."
Mr. Xu,
using cash is too much trouble.
Why don't you just wire the money
to my bank account?
Lawyer Xu,
here's today's "Legal Times."
What's in your hands?
These are files on the Hongchang Coal Mining case.
Lawyer wang asked me to get them to him.
Brother Zhang, the other day...
Right over there, behind the hillside.
The sheep were there.
But I didn't see Lei.
"News report about Hongchang Coal Mining
winning the lawsuit."
Wenjie, time for dinner.
Almost done.
Granny cooks the best shrimps.
Sweetie, you should have more.
"Hongchang's owner Mr. Chang
was acquitted of the charge."
"The company has mining
rights inside Gufeng Mountain."
"It owns several dozen mines in the region."
"Local conflicts and environmental
concerns caused by its mining operations"
"have always been the focus
of attention in the region."
Granny cooks the best shrimps.
Is Mr. Wang coming or not?
Mr. Li,
try this lamb, tastes good.
I'm a Buddhist. No meat for me.
It's a bad habit.
Sheep
are vegetarians too.
Let the chef take care of the rest of the lamb.
Vacuum wrap the meat and send it to Xiaobao.
My kid is abroad and never likes the food there.
Mr. Li,
I remember your child is also in Canada.
Wanna keep some for your son?
He's fine. Enjoy yourself.
Sorry, I have to leave now. See you later.
Mr. Li,
your driver asked me to tell you
he quit.
Chang Wannian! What are you up to?
Mr. Chang,
it wasn't me
that told on you.
It's not my fault.
Our mining business.
Nobody knows it better than we do.
There're lots of mines in Gufeng Mountain.
They either use my trucks or my machines.
You're the only one
that has nothing to do with me.
Chang...
You've got the wrong person.
I...
The mining licenses for the two valleys
are yours, right?
Sign here,
as the price of your betrayal.
Brother Chang, forgive me this time please.
You know that,
mining licenses cannot be traded.
It's illegal
I don't just want your licenses.
I'm asking you to sell me your company.
Hurry up,
before the meat cutter finishes the slicing,
sign the contract.
Let it sleep inside.
Lei made the bed for it.
That's terrible efficiency
I reported the case days ago.
You promised you could find the ox.
But where is it now?
I'm worried as hell.
Calm down.
You have no idea how worried I am!
My family depends on the ox.
This is our office. Please keep your voice down.
Is your son able to talk?
So, what's wrong with you?
Have you offended someone
in this village?
Early this morning,
I went to the temple and prayed
to the Gods to let Lei come back safe and sound.
I also asked for some food from the temple.
Here, have some.
Xia,
do you think
it's Ding Hai that did it?
Baomin went to his restaurant
as soon as he came back.
Lei was not there.
How much do you owe him?
A large sum.
We repay him every month.
But we spent a lot on the doctor's fee,
plus all the medicine.
So, we didn't pay him for two months.
But he didn't come after us.
It's only one eye.
It wouldn't cost us that much.
Is he blackmailing us?
Baomin, this idiot.
He should have listened to chief Liu,
signed the contract and taken the money
at that time.
Mom,
please don't talk about this in front of him.
Hey!
Who are you?
"My son is missing."
You're looking for your child?
Did anyone see this kid?
Time to go back to work!
You're from Gufeng Village?
That's quite a long way from here.
Eat something first.
Everybody li...
Hello?
Everybody listen up!
I won't repeat myself.
We've bought Jinquan Mining Company.
Now get your things and get the hell outta here.
Those sons-of-bitches are back again.
Come on
Who do you think you are?
Why the hell should we listen to you?
What about our pay?
Looks like we're gonna fight this time.
You bastards!
Come and stir up trouble again and again.
You really think we're soft?
Let's teach them a lesson!
Hit them!
Especially those at the front!
Brother Chang, listen to me.
Someone broke the car window.
The windshield.
A young man.
He can fight.
Stop fighting!
He's not working here.
He's looking for his son.
Stop! Shut up!
They say he doesn't work in the mine.
He is looking for his child.
This kid...
I saw this kid once.
Xia,
I had Master Hu tell our fortune.
He said that Lei would be back no matter what.
Take this talisman,
burn one piece every night.
Lei will definitely be back
in three days.
But keep it a secret,
don't let Baomin know.
You dumb?
Your son can wait.
You smashed the window?
It's not enough.
This is our boss's car.
I don't have a say.
How about,
you come with me.
Lad, you can't go with them.
He's lying.
Hello, Lawyer Xu.
Wenjie,
come here for a moment.
Mr. Xu,
regarding Hongchang Mining
Company's illegal mining case,
we'd like to ask you some questions.
How did you come to know
Hongchang's owner, Chang wannian?
Wait here.
Come in.
The windshield is broken.
He's a mute,
but he can hear all right.
I hear your son is missing.
On which day?
You saw the kid?
Yes...
It was the 12th when I got back from the mine.
At a crossroad in town,
I saw a kid standing there.
I was wondering,
it was almost nighttime
but how come the kid was still there.
I didn't see clearly in the dark.
What's the kid's name?
"Zhang Lei"
You're from Gufeng Village?
The boss is talking to you.
What's your name?
You a farmer?
"Zhang Baomin, miner in Feng county"
Ask our miners to keep an eye out.
Yes, Sir.
Well, send him back.
But the window...
You don't have to worry about it.
When you find the kid,
come and work in my mine.
Hello, we are from the procuratorate.
Is Mr. Chang here?
Wait a moment, please.
You think you could avoid us?
You don't have to pay
but we will return the favor.
Stay the fuck away from me, remember?
It's done.
Xia,
are you at home?
Shuanzi, come on in.
Lei still isn't back?
No, not yet.
Xia,
is the swelling on your leg getting better?
I don't think so.
This is the medicine my mom
mentioned last time.
It's cheaper but works even better.
She's been taking it for a while.
She told me to bring you some.
You can have a try.
Thanks to your mom.
Sick as she is,
she always thinks of me.
The water from the well tastes worse now.
Brother Zhang isn't home?
He's out looking for Lei.
It's really odd.
Where can he possibly be?
By the way,
after Brother Zhang left my place that day,
something just came to me.
Not sure if it's related to Lei's disappearance.
Don't let me see you again, you damn mute.
Or I'll beat your ass up every time I see you.
Bye, Shuanzi.
Give my regards to your mom.
It's fine. Go back inside.
Brother Zhang! You're back.
What happened?
What took you so long?
Did you fight with somebody again?
You...
Shuanzi is here to tell you something.
When I returned after looking for Lei,
I saw a car parked in the valley.
It didn't look like a car from our village.
It was gone the next day.
What happened, Baomin?
He must have been in a fight again.
Again? You serious?
It was not a jeep.
It was a silver-grey sedan.
Yes, almost like this.
It's silver-grey.
Your answer and the evidence we've gathered so far
are quite contradictory.
So, we'll be back.
I've told you everything I know.
For other matters you should go
to my Lawyer Xu.
Xu Wenjie is no longer a lawyer.
We suspect that he committed perjury in this case.
That's obstruction of justice.
We'll continue to investigate him.
You'd better think this through.
Deferral does no good to you.
You should cooperate with us
and report any wrongdoing.
It is in your own interest.
But Xu Wenjie
won't tell you this.
Hello.
The number you have dialed is busy now.
Please try your call again.
The baby bunnies' mom
picked fruits and vegetables from the mountain.
She arrived at her house
and knocked on the wooden door.
Sweeties. Open the door
Your mama is back.
It's not right. Tell it again.
Your voice doesn't sound like
the bunnies' mother's.
Sweeties.
Open the door!
Your mama is back.
No, no Tell it again.
Yuanyuan, be a good girl.
Daddy is really tired today.
I'll read it to you another day, all right?
When is Mom coming back?
Mama...
Your mother... She will...
come back after you enter middle school.
Liar!
It's all your fault!
Done
Move along and make some room!
Move! Move!
Hurry up!
Hello!
You guys on your way?
Hurry up! Just over the hill.
Be quick!
Let's hurry!
It's not working, boss. We have to push it.
Boss!
Come on
Here!
Move fast!
Come on
Be quick! Come on!
Move it!
Don't lose him!
Hurry up!
Let's go after him separately.
Where is he?
He can't get far with the child.
Keep running!
The Environmental Protection Bureau
has kept a closer eye lately.
Shall we stop mining for a while?
Mr. Chang,
coal prices have kept rising recently
and the Jinquan mine has a pretty good yield.
If we don't take this chance
to speed up the production,
it would be a great loss.
But the Bureau has...
Lawyer Xu,
you finally call back.
Did you kidnap my daughter?
You have some things I want, don't you?
What things?
I don't know what you're talking about.
In that case, I'm sorry.
I have no idea where your daughter is.
He's there
Go
"I saved your daughter. Meet me under the
stone tablet in Yingpanwan town. Be quick!"
Zhang Baomin!
Give me the girl back
Hello? Hello?
Everybody in the car!
Let's wait at his home.
He'll be home.
Baomin!
Baomin, where have you been?
I'm looking for you.
He's here!
Don't let him get away again!
Hurry
Hey!
Did you see a man running by?
Move!
They're gone.
Have you found your kid?
You're good-for-nothing.
Zhang Baomin!
Believe me or not,
we have your son
If you want your son back,
bring the girl back immediately.
Take some more guys,
get him as soon as he shows up.
Now go!
We lost the girl.
We ran after him all over the mountain
but he still got away.
A piece of bone is stuck in the cutter.
Is this him?
Not really.
No glasses.
Who are you looking for?
Is he out of his mind?
Whose turn is this?
Mr. Chang,
don't worry.
He has no other way but to return the girl.
I told him
that I had his son.
Mr. Chang...
Excuse me,
do you have a charger? I want to borrow it.
There's a socket under the table.
Thanks.
Sorry.
What are you doing!
Lei?
Baomin?
Is that you?
Is Zhang Baomin home?
You got us wrong.
See?
Your son is not here.
My man wanted the girl back.
So, he lied to you.
Where's the girl?
Lawyers can help find missing kids?
Sometimes we take child trafficking cases.
Trafficking?
Is there any chance to get the kids back?
Of course.
But it's hard to say.
I took one similar case not long ago.
When I was in town,
I saw the Missing Persons notice.
So, I called your husband,
see if I could meet him
and help out.
But he didn't show up.
Do you know where he's most likely to be?
You talked to him on the phone?
I texted him.
He is unable to make phone calls.
How come?
He bit off his tongue in a fight
when he was young.
He's been mute ever since.
He hasn't found our son.
Now, he's even lost himself.
You've made such a mess in my company.
I won't seek punishment,
as long as you give the girl back.
Hello?
Is this Zhang Baomin?
Can you hear me?
Where's my daughter?
Send a message to me, OK?
Hello?
"Your daughter is safe.
See you 8am tomorrow at Gufeng mountain."
"Send."
Lawyer Xu,
I'll tell my husband to contact you
as soon as he is back.
Please help us find our son!
Daddy?
Daddy...
Mom.
Wenjie, where are you?
Have you found Yuanyuan?
Please rest assured.
It won't take long before I find her.
Some policemen came.
They want to talk to you.
So, I told them about Yuanyuan.
Hold on a second.
Xu Wenjie,
where are you right now?
Yuanyuan!
Zhang Baomin!
Where's my daughter?
Where's my daughter!
Yes, that's her!
Where is she?
Freeze!
Give me back my things.
Or you'll never see your daughter again.
What "things"?
He has nothing to do with this.
Let him go first.
If I don't get my stuff,
nobody can leave.
I don't know what you want.
Evidence.
What evidence?
You're a lawyer.
Of course you know what evidence is
Let him go.
This is only between us.
Do you know?
His son is missing!
I know his son is missing.
Stay still!
Otherwise...
Keep still
Do you want to kill him as well?
You!
You want evidence, right?
I am the evidence!
You called the police?
Thank you.
Stop!
Where's my daughter?
Yuanyuan!
Daddy!
Yuanyuan, Yuanyuan.
Yuanyuan...
Yuanyuan.
Daddy...
Daddy will take you home.
Let's go back home.
Go home.
The cops are here.
What shall we do?
You still have a daughter to take care of.
I believe you'll fix it.
I understood that illegal mining
was a severe crime.
So, I sent for a lawyer.
That was how I met Xu wenjie.
If convicted,
Chang Wannian
would be sentenced to at most five years.
He asked me to help him win the case.
So, I told him
if he managed to win the case,
I would pay whatever he wanted.
After I got enough information,
secretly,
I went to several key witnesses
and bribed them to lie in court.
He took care of everything.
Once the verdict was out,
I only needed to pay some fines.
I was really satisfied.
So, I offered him 500,000 Yuan in cash
as a reward.
Lawyer Xu,
what do you like to do in your spare time?
Nothing special.
Your bow
looks quite unique.
This...
is very powerful.
I really needed the money.
Anything else you wish to confess?
Nothing.
Anything else you want to tell us?
Hey, Kiddo!
How much is your sheep?
Nothing.
Hansheng,
go back inside and eat your meal!
What are you drawing here all day?
I'm talking to you!
Go back inside and eat your meal!
"The police expanded their investigation
based on the new report."
"Xu Wenjie and Chang wannian were eventually
arrested but Zhang Lei's body has not been found."